Greenbaum, Marcia Papers 6091
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitration Documents: 1992 NY Telephone-- Stide Rite. (Box 47)
  - CWA And New York Telephone Company, Respondent Dismissal Vol. II, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Communications Workers of America, and New York Telephone Company, Dismissal (Vol. III), 1992 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Communications Workers of America And New York Telephone Company Dismissal, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Communication Workers of America And New York Telephone Company Dismissal, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - New York Telephone Co. ARB 1992 and CWA 1-92-111 NYT A-92-151 CWA Improper Work Completions, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Town of Norton, MA ARB 1992 and AAA #22 390 01105 92 Police Assn. Sick Leave, 1992-1995 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Ocean State Steel ARB 1992 and AAA #10-300-0016-92 United Steelworkers, Loc. 16031 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - City of Providence, RI ARB 1992 and AAA #10 390 0350 92 Turnb1 RI Laborers Dist. Council Loc. 1033, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - RI Commissioner of Education 1992 and AAA #10 390 0278 92 ESL/SS postr (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - S.D. Warren/Scott Paper CO. 1992 and AAA #11300 0062 92 GR. ME United Paperworkers Intl. Loc. 9 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - S.D. Warren Company ARB 1992 and AAA #11 300 01675 92 #92 132 United Paperworkers I.U.L. 1069, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Shaw's Supermarkets Inc. 1992 and AAA #11 300 01283 92 UFCW, Loc. 791 Sun. hrs. meat dept. (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - City of Springfield MA ARB 1992 and AAA #11 390 01158 92 bu wk IB Police O, Local 364 Non-unitees, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Stop & Shop Companies ARB 1992 and AAA #11 300 00524 92 United Food & Comm. Workers (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Stride Rite ARB 1992 and AAA #11 300 0790 92 United Food & Comm. W. Loc. 1445 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Arbitration Documents: 1992 Suburban Propane-- WGBH Ed.. (Box 48)
  - Suburban Propane ARB 1992 and FMCS 93-02378 OCAW, Local 8-366 Discharge (Folder 1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Suburban Propane ARB 1992 and FMCS 93-02378 OCAW, Local 8-366 Discharge (Folder 2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Suburban Propane and OCAW, Local 8-366 In RE: Discharge (Vol. I and II), 1992 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Suburban Propane & Petrolane and OCAW, Local 8-366, Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Union in RE: Discharge (Vol. II and III), 1993 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Suburban Propane & Petrolane and OCAW, Local 8-366, Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Union (Vol. IV), 1993 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Suburban Propane & Petrolane and OCAW, Local 8-366, Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Union in RE: Discharge (Vol.III) `, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Suburban Propane & Petrolane, Claimant vs. OCAW, Local 8-366, Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, Respondent Union in RE: Discharge (Vol.III), 1993 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Tufts University ARB 1992 and AAA #11300 00007 92 Service EES Intl. Un. Local #254 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Union Camp Corp. ARB 1992 and AAA #11 300 01195 92 UPIU, Local 902 Subcontracting (Folder 1 of 2), 1992-1994 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Union Camp Corp. ARB 1992 and AAA #11 300 01195 92 UPIU, Local 902 Subcontracting (Folder 2 of 2), 1992-1994 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - United Cable Co. GR. MED and Mrep 200-202 Catv-1-2 Intl. Bro. Elec. Wkrs., Loc. 2320, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Warner Lambert, Inc. ARB 1992 and AAA #11 300 00928 92 IBFO, Loc. 3 M. DeGois Shift chg., 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Warwick, RI School Comm. 1992 and AAA #10 390 0142 92 ARB Warwick Teachers Union, 1992-1994 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Warwick RI School Comm. 1992 and AAA #10 390 0150 92 ARB Warwick Teachers Union #17 VetHS, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Warwick, RI School Comm. 1992 and AAA #10 390 0189 92 ARB Warwick Teachers Union, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Warwick, RI School Comm. 1992 and AAA #10 390 0211 92 ARB Warwick Teachers Union #42 DHds, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Warwick, RI School Comm. 1992 and AAA #10-390-0212-92 Vacancies Warwick Teachers Union Gr. #52, 1992-1994 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Warwick, RI School Committee 1992 and AAA #10 390 348 92 ARB Warwick Teachers union, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Westerly, RI School Committee and AAA #10-390-0148-90 ARB R,I.L.D.C. Local 15, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Westwood, Ma School Comm. 1992 and AAA #11 290 00964 92 Tier Westwood Teachers Assn. Sick Lv., 1991-1994 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - WGBH Educational Foundation 1992 and Griev. #91-9 ARB Direct (Box 48, Folder 21)
- 1) Arbitration Documents: 1992 (continued) Whittier-- Woonsocket (end of Chronological order, start of alphabetical by project); 2) Airline Pilots Association, Chicago, IL. In the matter of Pan American London Transferees (Group 42) and Pre-Acquisition (Box 49)
  - Wiremold Company ARB 1992 and AAA #12 300 0332 92 Girard IBEW, Local 1040 Termination, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Whittier Regional School Comm. ARB and AAA #11 390 00176 92 1992 Whittier Regional ED. Assn. disch, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Woonsocket, RI School Comm. 1992 and AAA #10-390-0255-92 ARB S Woonsocket Teachers Guild, 1991-1993 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - ALPA, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - ALPA PAA/UAL Subject Files (Folder 1 of 2), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - ALPA PAA/UAL Subject Files (Folder 2 of 2), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Pan American London Transferees (Group 42) and Pre-Acquisition United Pilots RE: Integration of Seniority Lists, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Pan American London Transferees and Pre-Acquisition United Pilots RE: Integration of Seniority Lists, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Brief of the Pan American Phase II Transferees and United Pilots, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - UAL Pilot Eligibility Seniority List (Folder 1 of 2), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - UAL Pilot Eligibility Seniority List (Folder 1 of 2), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - UAL 1990 Pilot Seniority List, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Pan American London Transferees ("Group of 42") and Pre-Acquisition United Pilots, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Pan American London Transferees ("Group of 42") and Pre-Acquisition United Pilots, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Pan American London Transferees ("Group of 42") and Pre-Acquisition United Pilots, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Pan American London Transferees ("Group of 42") and Pre-Acquisition United Pilots, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - PDF Report #8E Pilot Eligibility Seniority List (Folder 1 of 2), 1990 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Airline Pilots Association, Chicago, IL. In the matter of Pan American London Transferees (Group 42) and Pre- Acquisition United Pilots. 1992. (Box 50)
  - PDF Report #8E Pilot Eligibility Seniority List (Folder 2 of 2), 1990 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - PDF Report #8E Pilot Eligibility Seniority List, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Volume A VAL Exhibits General History (Folder 1 of 2), 1990 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    Contains one photograph
  - Volume A VAL Exhibits General History (Folder 2 of 2), 1990 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Pan AM Phase II Transferees/ "Group of 42" PAA X 44, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - United Air Lines October 1990 Domicile Roster PAA X 73 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Seniority Range of Captains, First Officers, and Second Officers by Base, Aircraft and Position, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Pan American London Transferees ("Group of 42") and Pre-Acquisition United Pilots XII 2561-2664 Edgard Landry, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - XI. 2337-2560 Akins, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - X. 2023-2336, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - IX. 1778-2022, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - VIII. 1560-1777, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - VII. 1334-1559, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - VI. 1048-1333, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - V. 811-1047, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Airline Pilots Association, Chicago, IL. IN the matter of Pan American London Transferees (Group 42) and Pre- Acquisition United Pilots. 1992 **included in box are Binders. (Box 51)
  - Vol. III Group of 42 Exhibit Book, 1988-1991 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Volume I PAA Group of 42 Exhibits (Folder 1 of 4), 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Volume I PAA Group of 42 Exhibits (Folder 2 of 4), 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Volume I PAA Group of 42 Exhibits (Folder 3 of 4) (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Volume I PAA Group of 42 Exhibits (Folder 4 of 4), 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Pre-Acquisition United Pilots Volume "B" (Folder 1 of 2), 1987-1992 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Pre-Acquisition United Pilots Volume "B" (Folder 2 of 2), 1987-1991 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Exhibits of the Pre-Acquisition United Pilots Volume C (Folder 1 of 2), 1986-1991 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Exhibits of the Pre-Acquisition United Pilots Volume C (Folder 2 of 2), 1986-1991 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- 1) Airline Pilots Association, Chicago, IL-- Pan Am and United Group 42. Exhibits Volume IIA, B 1992; 2) Bryant Faculty Federation- Local 1769, AFT and Bryant College. Case No. AAA 1130-0583-77. 1977-1979; 3) Brookline School Custodians Association a (Box 52)
  - PAA Group of 42 Exhibits Volume II A ALPA, 1985-1992 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - PAA Group of 42 Exhibits Volume II B ALPA, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Bryant- Subject File, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Bryant College of Business Administration and Bryant Faculty Federation, Local 1769, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Bryant- Subject File, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Bryant College and AAA #1130-0583-77 ARB Bryant Faculty Federation, Loc. 1769 ARB, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Bryant College/FEDN. Notes, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Bryant College /Federation 1972-6/75, 1972-1974 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Bryant College/ Federation 1975-1976, 1972-1976 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Bryant College/ Federation 9/76-12/76, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Bryant College/ Federation 1/77-6/77, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Brookline School Committee and 1979 Brookline School Custodians, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Brookline School Committee Fact Finding 79 Direct and Brookline School Custodians (Folder 1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Brookline School Committee Fact Finding 79 Direct and Brookline School Custodians (Folder 2 of 2), 1975-1980 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Mass. Board of Regents of Higher Education and the Mass. Teachers Association (N. Adams State College Chapter) 1989. (Box 53)
  - Mass. Board of Regents of Higher and ** No. Adams State Col. Mass. Teachers Assoc. ARB 1989, 1991-1992 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Mass. Board of Regents of Higher and Education-North Adams St. Col. Mass. Teachers Assn. ARB 1989, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Agreement Between the Board of Regents of Higher Education and The Massachusetts Teachers Association/NEA 1986-89, 1986- 1989 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Board of Regents of Higher Education (North Adams State College) and North Adams State College CH. Mass. State College Assn. Massachusetts Teachers Assn., 1990 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - The Board of Regents of Higher Education and The MA Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol. I, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - The Bd. Of Regents of Higher Edu. And The MA Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol. II, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - The Bd. of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol. II, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - The Bd. of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol. IV, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - The Bd. of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter), 1989 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - The Bd. of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol. V, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - The Bd. of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol. VI, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - The Bd. of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol. VII, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - The Bd. of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol. VIII, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - The Bd. Of Regents of Higher Education and The MA Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol. IX, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - The Bd. of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol.X, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - The Bd. Of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA. Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol XI, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - The Bd. Of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA. Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol XII, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - The Bd. Of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA. Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol XIII, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - The Bd. Of Regents of Higher Education and The MA. Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol. XIV, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - The Bd. Of Regents of Higher Edu. and The MA. Teachers Assn. (North Adams State College Chapter) Vol. XV, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- 1) Mass. Board of Regents of Higher Education and the Mass. Teachers Association (N. Adams State College Chapter) 1989; 2) Mass. Higher Education Coordinating Council (Framingham St. College) and Mass. State College Association. 1989. (Box 54)
  - Mass. Board of Regents Cont. and The Mass Teachers Association (N. Adams St. College) Subject File (Folder 1 of 2), 1983-1990 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Mass. Board of Regents Cont. and The Mass Teachers Association (N. Adams St. College) Subject File (Folder 2 of 2), 1983-1990 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Book 1 Tenure Evaluation Materials, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Research Assn. X 2, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Tenure File Dr. Suzanne Carroll Eng./ Comm. Addendum Book III, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Book IV Major Responses to Tenure Committee, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Suzanne Carroll Book V VIII A.I.C. VIII A.I.d., 1988 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Book VI Assn. X 6 Assn. X 13, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Grievance Documents Info Requests J X 2, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - MA Higher Edu. Coordinating Council (Framingham State College) and Massachusetts State College Association JX-31, 32, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - MA Higher Edu. Coordinating Council (Framingham State College) and Massachusetts State College Association CX-5, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - MA Higher Edu. Coordinating Council (Framingham State College) and Massachusetts State College Association, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - MA Higher Edu. Coordinating Council (Framingham State College) and Massachusetts State College Association, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - MA Higher Edu. Coordinating Council (Framingham State College) and Massachusetts State College Association Salem State, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - MA Higher Edu. Coordinating Council (Framingham State College) and Massachusetts State College Association CX-4, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - MA Higher Edu. Coordinating Council (Framingham State College) and Massachusetts State College Association JX-28,29,30, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - MA Higher Edu. Coordinating Council (Framingham State College) and Massachusetts State College Association, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - MA Higher Edu. Coordinating Council (Framingham State College) and Massachusetts State College Association, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - MA Higher Edu. Coordinating Council (Framingham State College) and Massachusetts State College Association, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - II-B(b) Research Unpublished Work Manuscript w/ Revisions, Appendices & Notes on Lotus and Dbase 10 of 11, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Mass. Higher Education Coordination Council (Framingham St. College) and Mass. State College Association. 1989. (Box 55)
  - Mass. Higher Ed. And Mass. A. College Association (Framingham St. College), 1989 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - II-A (b) Memberships or Participation in Professional Organizations 8 of 11, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - II-C Relevant Graduate Study 11 of 11, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - II-A (a) Memberships or Participation in Professional Organizations 7 of 11, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - I-B Artistic or Creative Activities 6 of 11, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - I-A (b) Committees 5 of 11, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - I-A (a) Pedagogy 4 of 11, 1985-1987 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Previous Years Evaluation 3 of 11, 1985-1987 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Appendix A-1 2 of 11 General and Latest Evaluation- 1989 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Summary 1 of 11, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Memorandums Relating to Framingham State College and Other Docs., 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Documents Relating to Framingham State College Economic Department, 1986-1990 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Docs. Relating to Framingham State College and Riel, 1985-1988 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Board of Regents Higher Education (Bridgewater State College) and Massachusetts State College Association a/w Massachusetts Teachers Association, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Mass. Bd. Of Trustees ARB 1990 and Framingham State College Mass. Teachers Assn.(Folder 1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Mass. Bd. Of Trustees ARB 1990 and Framingham State College Mass. Teachers Assn.(Folder 2 of 2), 1992 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Documents Relating to Framingham State College, 1989-1990 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- New Hampshire Cases: Mediation and Fact Finding 1988, 1989. (Box 56)
  - Amherst, NH School Board Med 1982 and NHPELRB # Amherst Education Assn., 1989 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Ashland, NH School Board FF 1988 and NHPELRB #T-0304:4 Fact Find Ashland Teachers Assn. NEA-NH (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - The Ashland Education Association and The Ashland School Board, 1985-1989 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Ashland School District Fact-Finding School Board Presentation February 10, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - The Franklin Education Association and The Franklin School Board, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Franklin NH School Board FF 1989 and NHPELRB# Franklin Education Assn. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Hollis, NH School Board Med 1989 and NHPELRB # T-0234: 7 NEA-NH Holiis Ed. Assn. & Support Staff (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Interlakes, NH School BD. Med. And Direct Mediation 1988 Interlakes Teachers, NEA-NH (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Inter-Lakes School District 1984-88 School Board and Professional Employees Agreement, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Inter-Lakes School Board Med. 1989 and NHPELRB # Inter-Lakes Educn. Assn. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Kensington, NH School Board FF 89 and NHPELRB # T-0311: 9 Fact Findg Kensington Education Assn., 1989 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Kensington Education Association Fact Finding, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Fact Finding Before Marcia L. Greenbaum and Agreement Btwn. Kensington School Board and Kensington Edu. Assn., 1989 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Litchfield, NH School Board and NHLRB Fact Finding Litchfield Education Assn. 1988 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Merrimack Valley School Bd. 1989 and NHPELRB #T-0387 :1 Mediation Merrimack Valley FEDN. Of T, NEA-NH, 1988-1989 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Northwood NH School Board 1988 and Mediation T-0325:2 Northwood Teachers Assn. NEA-NH (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Raymond, NH School Board Med. 1989 and NHPELRB #T-0252-6 Raymond Teachers Organization, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Seaboard World Airlines Pre-Merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line Pre-Merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line, Inc. (The Merged Company) 1982. (Box 57)
  - Seaboard World Airlines Pre-Merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line Pre-Merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line, Inc. (The Merged Company), 1983 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Flying Tigers/Seaboard World Air and Seniority List Integration Flight Attendants Master File, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Seaboard World Airlines Pre-Merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line Pre-Merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line, Inc. (The Merged Company), 1983 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Flying Tigers Seaboard World Air and Seniority List Integration Flight Attendants Drafts, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Flying Tigers/Seaboard World Air and Seniority List Integration Flight Attendants Lists, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - FTL/SWA/AFA Working Papers, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Flying Tiger/ Seaboard World Air and Proudural Case Flight Attendants Association, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - FTL-SWA Flight Attendants Furlough Award, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Flying Tigers/Seaboard World Air and Seniority List Integration Flight Attendants Notes, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Flying Tigers/Seaboard World Air and Srsanb Wates Flight Attendants Association, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Integration of Seaboard World and Flying Tigers Flight Attendants Seniority Lists, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Integration of Seaboard World and Flying Tigers Flight Attendants Seniority Lists II, II IV, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Integration of Seaboard World and Flying Tigers Flight Attendants Seniority List s V, VI, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Integration of Seaboard World and Flying Tigers Flight Attendants Seniority List s VII, VIII, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Seaboard World Airlines Pre-Merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line Pre-Merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line, Inc. (The Merged Company), 1983 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Seaboard World Airlines Pre-merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line Pre-Merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line, Inc. (The Merged Company), 1983 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Seaboard World Airlines Pre-Merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line Pre-Merger Flight Attendant Group and Flying Tiger Line, Inc. (The Merged Company) 1982. (Box 58)
  - Flying Tigers/Seaboard World Air and Seniority List Integration Flight Attendants Prior ARB. AWD, 1977-1981 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - FTL/AFA Employment, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Flying Tigers/Seaboard World Air and Seniority List Integration Flight Attendants Chronology, 1978-1980 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Documents Relating to Seaboard and Flying Tigers Airlines, 1978-1980 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Documents Relating to The Flying Tiger Line, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Direct Excerpts from Direct Examination of Charles Kurth, Cross-Examination and Direct Rebuttal Examination Exhibit B-4 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Flying Tiger Pilot Exhibits D-1 Through D-54 Inclusive, as Identified in Flying Tiger Flight Attendants Exhibit R-8, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - FTL Pilot Exhibits RD-1 through RD-23 Inclusive, As Identified in FTL FA Ex, R-8, 1977-1980 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Flying Tiger Flight Attendants "A" Exhibits, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Flying Tiger Flight Attendants "R" Exhibits (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - SWA FA Book A MG, 1978-1981 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Book B SWA FA MG, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Flying Tiger Flight Attendants "C" Exhibits, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Flying Tiger Flight Attendants "B" Exhibits, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Involving Merger of Seniority Lists, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Flying Tiger Lines, Inc. and Seaboard World Airlines, Inc. Merger of Seniority Lists, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Flying Tigers/Seaboard World Air and Seniority List Integration Flight Attendants Supporting Mat., 1981 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Agreement Btwn. Flying Tiger Line Inc. and Flight Attendants, Note Cards and Agreement btwn, Seaboard World Airlines, Inc., 1980- 1982 (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Texas International Airlines Pilots Group and Continental Airlines Pilots Group in the matter of Pilot Seniority Integration: contains: Alpha merger policy, proposals, employment data, entitlements, and portion of master file. 1983. (Box 59)
  - Alpha Merger Policy, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Some (water?) damage to documents
  - Volume V Flight Engineers A Case Study of Technological Unemployment, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Some damage to first sheet of paper in file
  - Volume VII Crossover Pilots, 1978-1983 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Some damage to left edge of file